<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Ross-Hunter: js</title>
  <subtitle>Posts tagged with js</subtitle>
  <id>http://www.ross-hunter.com</id>
  <link href="http://www.ross-hunter.com"/>
  <link href="http://www.ross-hunter.com/tag/js/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2018-12-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Ross Hunter</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>CoffeeScript jQuery Animated Scrolling Sidebar</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.ross-hunter.com/2012/06/03/floating-coffee-bar/"/>
    <id>http://www.ross-hunter.com/2012/06/03/floating-coffee-bar/</id>
    <published>2012-06-03T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2020-04-14T10:51:48-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Ross Hunter</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">I have been really getting into writing CoffeeScript lately, so I decided to revisit the jQuery floating sidebar I blogged about a while back. The logic is the same, other than using a named function to increase readability. The code is shrunk from 40 lines to 28 lines (with extra line breaks for readability). More importantly, I believe the code is easier to understand.
The basic concept is to create</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Creating an Animated Floating Sidebar With jQuery</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.ross-hunter.com/2011/05/08/floating-jquery-bar/"/>
    <id>http://www.ross-hunter.com/2011/05/08/floating-jquery-bar/</id>
    <published>2011-05-08T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2020-04-14T10:51:48-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Ross Hunter</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">I finally got around to implementing a floating sidebar that contains all of my follow links contained in my header. Lots of sites have a floating sidebar, but I wanted mine to be a little different. First, the items in my sidebar come flying out of the header to the sidebar 
when the user scrolls down past the header, instead of being fixed over on the side. You will also notice a nifty little elastic</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>jQuery Masonry is Bad Ass</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.ross-hunter.com/2011/04/04/masonry/"/>
    <id>http://www.ross-hunter.com/2011/04/04/masonry/</id>
    <published>2011-04-04T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2020-04-14T10:51:48-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Ross Hunter</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">jQuery Masonry is a sweet layout plugin for jQuery. They describe it as “The flip side of CSS floats”. It aligns elements vertically then horizontally, minimizing the vertical gaps between elements of varying heights. I created my own sandbox for playing around with masonry.

Like any layout, it has it’s time and place. I would consider this primarily an alternative layout, only to be used when trying</summary>
  </entry>
</feed>
